(Bernadette:)I'm too small for Twister.
And roller coasters.
(Bernadette:)And sitting with my feet on the floor.
(Bernadette:)Hope you enjoyed
the prenatal cigarettes, mom.
Hey, my mom smoked pot
when she was pregnant with me...
(Penny:)...and I turned out just fine.
(Penny:)Hey, look, I have peach schnapps.
Thank God.
- Guys, something happened.
- What's wrong?
(Amy:)I think a boy likes me.
"Hi. It's Stuart.
We met at the comic book store.
(Bernadette(reading):)I was wondering if you'd like to get
coffee sometime. It's okay if you say no.
(Bernadette(reading):)It might be the kick in the pants I need
to start taking Zoloft."
Amy, you little vixen.
(Penny:)Just working it under all those layers
of wool and polyester.
What are you gonna do?
Doesn't he know you have a boyfriend?
(Penny:)Oh, she doesn't have a boyfriend,
she has a Sheldon.